导演：汤尼 史考特
主演：布鲁斯 威利
迪蒙威 恩斯
终极尖兵
周五夜,是橄榄球狂欢夜
你可以感受到那股气氛
就像夜深时的闪电
你可四处感受到
因为今晚在克里夫兰 将是狂欢时刻
周五夜,是橄榄球狂欢夜
雄马队和大猫队
将一决胜负
周五夜,是橄榄球狂欢夜
坐稳,放轻松
让群众通过
这将是场艰辛的奋战
我们将享有一个
狂欢的橄榄球夜
在这个肉身赤博的丛林
每个失误都会引来隆隆吼声
失误引来吼声
每个座位都像五十号线
保证你会有个狂欢夜
周五夜,是橄榄球狂欢夜
雄马和大猫
将一决胜负
周五夜,是橄榄球狂欢夜
坐稳,放轻松 让我们静下心来观赏
这将是场艰辛的奋战
我们将享有一个 狂欢的橄榄球夜
周五夜,是橄榄球狂欢夜
今晚是周五夜
从这儿获得满足吧
绿衫88
Green 88!
开始
各位先生女士
That ends the first half of play...
上半场比赛结束
比数是克里夫兰队十七分
with the score: Cleveland 17, Los Angeles 10.
洛杉矶队十分
快走,快,快
Let's go! Move!
比利柯尔,比利柯尔
Billy Cole!
上半场一团糟
The first half stunk!
把洞打开
Open the holes up! Get in there like pigs!
尽力去打
比利柯尔…你的电话,三线
Billy Cole.
我们要认真打
Call on line 3.
以赢家姿态离城
Let's kick some butt. Let's get out of this town a winner!
我讨厌克里夫兰队
I hate Cleveland!
哈
Hello, William. This is milo.
嗨,威廉,我是麦洛
今晚有不少钱 投入在这场比赛上
There's a lot of money on this game.
你最好能达阵得分,威廉
You better score some touchdowns.
不择手段地去做,懂吗?
Do whatever it takes. Understood?
否则你就过气了
Or else you're history.
欢迎观赏在克里夫兰 体育馆的下半场球赛
It's the second half. We're in Cleveland...
今晚由洛城雄马队
for this game between the I.A. stallions and Cleveland cats.
对克里夫兰大猫队
我是朗魁 他是我的搭档巴克
I'm vern lundquist with dick butkus. And yes, friends...
朋友们,今晚的雨真是大
it really is that wet.
虽然雄马队以十比十七落后
Vern, even though the stallions traii 17-10...
有个人的脚步仍很轻松
there walks a happy man, Sheldon marcone, owner of the I.A. stallions.
那就是谢利马康
他是雄马队的老板
他的球队 在西岸胜六场输二场
His team tops the Western division at 6-2.
谢顿现正接受 我们休恩的访问
Sheldon is with Lynn Swann now.
让我们听听
- Let's go to them. - 29,256.
4万九千余人…
以今晚的重要性而言 球迷进场人数似乎蛮少的
That's pretty poor attendance, wouldn't you say?
你怎么说? 我不予置评,休恩
I wouldn't say.
你能解释下,球迷减少 及收视率降低的原因?
Explain the attendance and TV ratings drop-off.
是否职业橄榄球面临绝境?
Is pro football dying?
不,我认为是 好的橄榄球报导正面临绝境
No, it's good journalism that's dying, Lynn.
马康先生 这场球赛有任何英雄吗?
Are there any heroes left in the game?
你在看那场球赛?
What game are you watching? Let's talk about heroes.
说到英雄
比利柯尔今晚出色极了
Billy Cole is having the game of his life tonight.
准备
准备好
第一次十分 把克队四分卫打倒了
First and 10 at the Cleveland 47-yard line.
第一十分,剩下不到两分钟
First and 10, 2 minutes left. It's probably I.A.'s final possession.
似乎是洛杉矶队的最后机会
雄马队要赢七分 靠踢球绝得不到
I.A. needs 7. A field goai will not do.
迪克一定在想：
You've got to be thinking: "Get the ball to Billy Cole. ".
要如何把球传给柯尔
丢
罗勃冲过层层关卡 要把球传给柯尔
The pass is complete to Billy Cole!
快跑!快跑!
生命是一团狗屎,不是吗?
Ain't life a bitch?
这人醉死了
Dude's trashed.
我们来整整他
We should do something to him.
来吧
Do it.
该死!
This dude is really trashed.
这家伙真是醉昏了
来,拿走他的表
Go on. Take his watch.
他有枪
He's got a gun!
这是贺伦堡侦探社
This is hallenbeck investigations. Leave your message at the beep.
请在哔一声后,留下口信
乔,我是麦可马休
Joe! Mike Matthews. I got a job for you.
我有份工作要给你
等一下,等一下
Hold on a minute.
麦可?乔?
I thought you were in Vegas. I was going to leave a message.
我以为你仍在拉斯维加斯
正准备留言机留言
你听来醉薰薰的 你昨晚做了什么?
You sound terrific.
我想我把支松鼠弄死了 但却记不得了
I think I fucked a squirrei to death.
听着,乔 你仍靠救济金过活吗?
You still taking charity?
你有什么工作? 是个舞女,不对
- What do you got? - Stripper. Excuse me, exotic dancer.
该说是个脱衣舞娘 某个怪胎缠住她了
Some weirdo's hassling her and I'm booked solid. She's hot.
她想找人监护她 但我早已排满
她很火热哦,乔 我给她三颗星…
Rates 3 on my finger scale.
如果我能跟她上床…
I'd cut off 3 fingers if God would let me fuck her.
砍下我三支指头,我都愿意
单凭你那个爱闻骚味的鼻子 我想她会满意吗?
Make her a one on your nose scale. Improve your looks.
去整你的那张脸吧
好吧,好吧...听着, 我很忙,你愿意接吗?
Yeah, eat me.
I'm booked. You got plans?
我现在只想好好抽根烟
I was going to smoke cigarettes.
可以迟点再做吗?
- Could you postpone? - These are pretty good cigarettes.
是很好的烟呢
有五百元酬劳,乔
It's 500 bucks.
我还有点玛事要做
I got to run some errands.
一小时后,到你办公室会面
Meet you in an hour.
梳好你的头发 我借你件好西装
Comb your hair. I'll lend you a nice jacket-
没有人喜欢你
nobody likes you.
每个人都讨厌你
Everybody hates you.
你铁定是要失败的
You're going to lose.
微笑吧,浑蛋
Smile, you fuck.
吉米?  是的
Jimmy?
你仍在吗?
You still here?
我想是吧
Guess I am.
救救我!
Help me!
雷,这女孩怎么回事?
Ray.
这婊子不肯口交
- What's with the giri, man? - Bitch won't blow me.
这么早就做这个 放她走吧,老兄
It's too early for that. Let her go.
她不肯做,我就不让她上来
She ain't coming up till she starts blowing.
她会淹死的,雷
She's going to drown, man.
干,你这失败者 放她走,雷
Fuck you, loser!
你在这干嘛? 这是球队的狂欢会
Let her go.
Why are you here? It's a league party. You got kicked out, remember?
你被开除了 记得吗?记得吗?
你这狗杂种!
You bastard!
上来,离开这儿,你这条猪
- Get out of here. - Pig!
干
You fuckhead!
我是国家橄榄球队最佳金臂手 最好记得,你这肥婊子
Best arm in the nationai league. Remember that, you fat son of a bitch!
嘿,乔
我以为你还在拉斯维加斯
I thought you were in Las Vegas.
本来是
I was.
你昨晚睡那?
Where'd you sleep?
办公室
The office.
嘿,毛茸茸
Furry tom.
你输了多少钱?
How much you lose?
我没有去赌钱
I wasn't there to gamble.
多少?
How much?
我只是打发跟踪时光
I was doing a skip trace.
五十元
50 bucks.
这是什么?
What is this?
圣诞老人,黛莲画的
Darian drew a holiday picture.
很显然地,她的老师想见我们
Obviously, her teacher wants to see us.
她在那里?
Where is she?
在朋友家
Slept at a friend's.
孩子们仍在笑她的牙套吗?
Boys giving her a hard time about the braces?
你在说笑吗?
Are you kidding? "Metai mouth" is the latest.
她的最新绰号是“钢牙”
Little bastards.
小杂种
她14岁时 就会让他们销魂了
She'll be screwing them when she's 14.
小心你的狗嘴,乔
Watch your mouth.
别来了 你让她化那么漂亮的妆…
You let her wear so much makeup she looks...
她简直像支沅熊
like a goddamn raccoon.
我回到家里 还以为有贼儿上门
I thought she was a burglar. I almost shot her twice.
差点两度射杀她
你的话并不好笑 每个女孩子都化妆上学
You're not funny. Girls wear makeup.
我知道,但不是个个都用喷漆啊
I'm sure they don't put it on with a paint sprayer.
告诉你吧…
For your information, a lot of people think I'm very funny.
很多人都认为我很风趣
那你去跟他们住吧
Go live with them.
别考验我
Don't tempt me.
衣柜内的男人是谁?
Who's the guy in the closet?
什么?
Excuse me?
有时,你忘了我是名侦探
You forget I'm a detective.
浴室内有蒸汽
There's all this steam in the shower.
但你的头发是干的 所以当然别有他人
Only your hair is dry. So it must be somebody else.
且是男的 因为马桶盖掀起来了
A male. The toilet seat's up.
床底没人 你一定把他藏在衣柜内
Since he's not under the bed...
因为你听到我的熄火声
I figure you must have stuck him in the closet.
那么…
究竟衣柜里的男人是谁?
Who's in the closet?
老天啊,一切没变
Jesus Christ, nothing changes.
你仍然像个疯子
You're still a lunatic.
要告诉我他是谁吗?
Will you tell me who?
你要我打开衣柜吗?乔
Shall I open the closet?
我会的
I'll do it. Then we'll both know you're psycho!
然后我们彼此知道
你是个大疯子 这就是你要的吗?
Is that what you want?
不是
Thank you.
谢谢
衣柜门仍是关上的
That door stays shut.
我要做的是数到三
What I'm going to do...
is count to 3.
然后我要向那扇门开枪
Then I'll put a bullet in that door.
只要你说出真相 随时我都可罢手
You can stop me by telling the truth.
1… 打电话给你心理医生
Call your shrink and tell him you're losing it.
告诉他你疯了
真相是件很美好的事
The truth is a beautifui thing.
2… 你怎敢在这里放肆
How dare you come into this house and-
并且开枪…不要 3…
听着,乔 替我暖床吗?麦可
- look, Joe- - Keeping her warm for me?
别紧张,别做傻事
Easy. Don't do nothing dumb.
她表现如何?
How was she?
你给我的老婆几分?
On your scale, how was my wife?
它就自然发生了,乔
It just happened.
当然,当然,我了解 它就自然发生了
Sure, I know.
It just happened.
它还可能发生在任何人身上
It could happen to anybody.
是个意外,对吗? 你在地板上翻来滚去
An accident.
然后不小心地把你的宝贝送上
You tripped and accidentally stuck your dick in my wife.
我真是抱歉,奸夫淫妇
"I'm so sorry, Mrs. h. I guess this just isn't my week."
我想本周不是我的幸运周
乔,请放下枪
Put the gun down.
哦,对了,枪
The gun.
是的,莎拉, 我想你说的没错
You're right.
我是疯了
I think I am losing it.
滚开
Get out of here.
头还是肚子,麦可?
Head or gut, Mike?
乔, 我们做朋友多久了?
Joe, how long we been friends?
我会说,在你姘上我老婆前
Roughly till you started banging my wife.
头还是肚子?
Head or gut?
肚子吧
Gut.
有地址要给我吗?
Got that address for me?
那份监护工作
The surveillance job.
你仍要…那份工作?
You still want the job?
五百元就五百元吧,麦可
500 bucks is 500 bucks, Mike.
是啊…
I guess you're right.
你说的没错
柯莉…?
Throw a shot into her?
你跟她也有一手,对吧?
滚开,去你的地盘拉屎
Get the fuck out of here. Go shit in your own yard.
乔?
Joe!
我在这里
Over here.
有人在车上装了炸弹
Somebody wired the car.
哪个家伙干的, 乔?
Who the fuck did this?
罗杰斯先生,我怎会知道?
Mr. Rogers.
How the hell should I know?
你告诉警察…
You told the cops?
我告诉他们 麦可今早刚好经过
I told them Mike came by to farm out a surveillance job.
想找个人接手那件监护案
That's all?
就这样?
你没有提…
You didn't mention...
没有,我没有提
No. I didn't mention it.
你早知道,对不对?
You knew, didn't you?
我曾怀疑过 该死,你就不能说点什么吗
I suspected.
Why didn't you say something?
你要我说什么,莎拉?
Say what?
“你去死,莎拉”?
"Fuck you, Sarah"?
是的,或者任何能让你怒火上升的话
Anything to get a rise out of you.
你何不说：你这说谎的婊子
"You're a iying bitch, Sarah," or "I'll spit in your face."
或者说：如果没有条子在这 我早就在你脸上吐口水了
你想这样吗?
Want me to spit on you?
那表示你还有一点自尊
- It would show you had pride. - Fresh out, honey.
这倒鲜,甜心
干,乔,你从不在身旁
Fuck you, Joe. You're never around. I was lonely!
我很寂寞 买只狗呀!
Buy a dog.
我并不恨你,乔
I'm not the one who hates you. You're the one who hates you.
但你却恨你自己
而我得和自己一起24小时
And I get to live with myself 24 hours a day.
脱光衣服
一夜之欢,变换22种姿势
脱光衣服…
敬亚历士这位太空人
Alex, the astronaut.
脱光衣服  敬亚历士
The astronaut.
上一次看到你 灌下一瓶伏特加酒
Last time I saw you drink straight vodka was because you cheated on Cory.
是你欺骗柯莉时
是啊,再帮我倒一杯
Why don't you pour me another?
老兄…
你以前不是这样的
You didn't.
你一定疯了, 伙计,敢欺骗她
You got to be crazy, cheating on her.
我一定得弄点名堂
I got to be something, harp. Because all I do is lose friends...
因为我现在所做的 就是失去朋友,喝酒
并捕获任何有心跳的东西
drink and naii anything with a heartbeat.
就如坐在酒吧旁这种事, 是吗?
Just stay on that side of the bar.
哦,说出来吧 脱光衣服
让女人成为女人
让男人成为男人
脱光衣服…
我现在付你钱吗? 不用
Should I pay now?
你不用现在付钱, 把钱收起来
No, you should not. Put the money away.
坐下
Sit down.
所以…
你认为警方帮不了你
The cops can't help?
没错,我死了
Sure. After I'm dead, they'll do the autopsy.
他们只会帮我验尸
我想你不能等那么久
Guess you can't wait that long.
没错
Guess not.
这地方只奏这种音乐?
This the only music they play here?
我讨厌这种狗屎音乐
I hate this funk shit.
或许我该额外收费
I may charge extra.
你期望会放什么音乐?
What'd you expect?
“四个新鲜人”,“白潘”
The four freshmen.
你是谁呀?我老爸呀! 是啊,我是你爸
Pat Boone.
Are you my father?
多穿点衣服上去 你真有趣
I'm your father. Put some clothes on.
You're hilarious.
这种气氛下, 把你的头放在喇叭旁
Stand by that speaker. You'll scream...
当奏起“播放你的放克音乐” 你会尖叫的白男孩
"...play that funky music, white boy!"
我相信我会尖叫
The screaming I believe.
嗨,帅哥
Hello, handsome.
嗯…
Who's the stiff over there?
那边那个死鬼是谁?
无名小卒
That's nobody.
轮到我跳了,妈的
It's my turn to dance. Shit.
我很抱歉
好的,好的, 让我们来介绍一位女人
Let's bring out a woman who's always in the mood.
她永远心情绝佳
把你的双掌放在一起
Put your hands together for the lovely and talented miss Cory!
为这位可爱,才华扬溢的
柯莉小姐鼓掌吧
骑在牧场上
我戴着帽子
穿着靴子
满身尘土
我骑着马鞍…
你是无名小卒
You're nobody.
别告诉别人
Don't tell anyone.
那是柯莉说的 柯莉说你是无名小卒
Cory says you're nobody.
放轻松点,小子 没人要扫你的兴
Nobody's raining on your parade. I'm keeping an eye on her.
我只是在监视柯莉
你是保镖之类的人物吗?
Are you some kind of bodyguard?
类似吧
Something like that.
有火吗?没有
Got a match?
柯莉有麻烦吗?
Is Cory in trouble?
我不知道,你说呢?
I don't know. You tell me.
她什么也没对我说
She didn't tell me.
所以你生气?
Does that piss you off?
也许吧
Maybe.
别担心
Don't sweat it.
女人都有秘密
Women have secrets.
就像水是湿的,天空是蓝的 女人有秘密是正常的
Water's wet, the sky's blue, women have secrets.
谁在乎?
Who gives a fuck?
要啤酒吗?
Want a beer?
她是查电话簿找到你的?
So she just hired you? What, you're in the book or something?
什么,你有列名在电话簿上
她请我的老友麦可帮她… 我只是来顶替他的
She hired my buddy, Mike. I'm filling in.
麦可人在哪?
Where's Mike?
他死了
He died.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry to hear that.
他是个浑蛋
He was an asshole.
听着,我不管你是谁 或是发生什么事
I don't know who you are or what's going on, but Cory's my giri.
但柯莉是我的女友
假如她惹上麻烦,我想知道
If she's in trouble, I want to know.
机密,大个子
Confidentiai, big boy.
不管怎样,告诉我
Why don't you tell me anyway?
不行
Nope.
你连一杯尿也保不住,老兄
Man, you couldn't protect a cup of warm piss.
你为何不上前打我?
Why don't you just hit me?
什么?
Excuse me?
来吧,胆小鬼
Chickenshit. Bust me in the chops. An old guy like me can't hurt you.
把我打的支离破碎呀!
像我这样的老头 伤不了你的,不是吗?吉米
看来你知我是谁了 吉米亚历山大迪克斯
You know who I am?
89～90年洛城雄马队四分卫
James Alexander dix. Quarterback for the I.A.
stallions, '89-'90.
因赌博被逐出球队
Banned from the league for gambling.
又被控吸毒
Allegations of drug abuse.
又是一个 浪费青春的悲惨例子
Another tragic tale of wasted youth.
现在你可惹毛我了 是时候了
You're pissing me off!
我是乔贺伦堡
It's about time.
Joe hallenbeck...
我是私家侦探 你是个下等人
private detective.
You're a lowlife.
至少我没去吸毒自毁前途
At least I didn't shit my talent away on coke.
我把我的尿弄倒了
Spilled my warm cup of piss.
柯莉,快来,我们走
- Get your shit. Let's go. - What's the matter with you?
吉米,你是怎么了?
吉米,闭嘴,别多管闲事
Shut up! Get in the cage.
好的,好的
It's cooi.
请为柯莉小姐鼓掌
Let's hear it for miss Cory!
是的,请鼓掌
（香烟,二元二角五分)
（请投票给班纳)
班纳
我不会投给你的, 你这狗杂种
I didn't vote for you, you son of a bitch.
我是个下等人
So I'm a lowlife.
就是他,他跟她一道
That's him. He was with her.
把他弄走,干掉他
Take him and kill him.
合约中没载明他
No contract on him.
那就免费做吧,到别处干
Then do it for free. Elsewhere.
敬亚历士,小儿科医生
Alex, the pediatrician.
如果我是支猫,就会咪咪叫
If I were a cat, I'd purr.
乖点
Behave!
我要你跟我回我住处
Come back to my place with me. I'll give you your birthday present.
我有生日礼物送你
像这个吗?
- Does it look like that? - Do you want it?
你要吗?是啊
- What is it? Give me a hint. - A hint?
是什么?给我点提示
提示?好的
你想重回老本行吗?
How'd you like to get your old job back?
继续走,进去里面
Go on. Get in there!
你来的不是时候 地点也不对
Wrong place, wrong time. Nothing personai.
又没有私人恩怨
那是你的想法
So you think. Last night I fucked your wife.
昨晚,我和你老婆上床
哦,真的吗?
You did? How did you know it was my wife?
你怎知道是我老婆
她说她老公一副老娼像 戴顶帽子
She said her husband looked like a pimp with a hat.
你真酷,一个吃子弹的人
You're cooi, for a guy about to take a bullet.
在干了你老婆后 我吃2颗子弹
After fucking your wife, I'll take 2.
来,告诉我
What's this about you getting me my old job back?
你要如何让我重回老本行?
他去哪里了?
Where the hell is he?
那侦探?
The detective?
你究竟有什么麻烦?
What kind of trouble you in?
麻烦?我没有惹任何麻烦
I'm not in trouble. Some creep's threatening me.
只是有人想恐吓我罢了
现在我们进去等乔贺伦伯吧
- Let's wait inside for hallenbeck. - What am I chopped liver?
我的心肝,你把我置于何处
贺伯伦是个游手好闲的人 他能做什么?
What's that bum going to do? Breathe on them?
点烟? 然后把烟吐在他们身上?
如果那个人出现, 我就打死他
If the creep shows up, I'll bitch-slap him.
来,我跟在你后面回家, 上车吧
I'll follow you home. Get in your car.
你会“打死他”?
You'ii "bitch-slap" him?
对,打死他
Yeah. Bitch-slap him.
好
啊,讨厌
你想在那开个洞? 胸口?
Where you want it? In the chest? Or the head?
还是头?
你老婆也是这么说的
So said your wife.
嘿,别再提我老婆
Stop with the wife shit!
问问我,她有多肥
Ask me how fat she is.
狗杂种
Fuck you!
她有多胖?
How fat is she?
胖到我要她在面粉堆滚才找得到阴部
So fat I had to roll her in flour and look for the wet spot.
你想和她做爱 还得打她的大腿,才能进去
To fuck her, you slap her thigh and ride the wave in.
说她胖吗?
I'm not saying she's fat.
她的高中毕业照 像是空中摄影
Her high schooi picture was an aeriai photograph.
你这狗杂种
You bastard!
And then some.
干!
Fuck!
柯莉,别下车
Don't get out.
你不懂驾车吗?
Can't you drive?
柯莉
狗屎
快滚开这里
Let's get the fuck out of here!
狗屎
倒车…
Back up!
Back up.
皮裤?
Leather pants.
是啊
这种东西要多少钱?
What's something like that run?
六百五
650.
六百五十元?是的
650 dollars?
一条裤子?是的
They're pants?
你穿这么贵的裤子? 是的
You wear them?
裹面有电视吗?
They don't have a TV in them?
没有
我太落伍了
I am very old.
真臭
Something stinks in here.
我的天啊,是这份笔录
It's this statement. Hallenbeck's hiding something.
这份口供全是狗屎 贺伦伯一定在隐瞒什么
你怎知道?
How do you know?
我知这鬼家伙心里想什么
I know how his mind works! Every lie has 80%...
有个谎言总有八成真
这才是令我害怕之处
truth to it. It's scary.
我们看到的是同一个人吗?
We looking at the same guy?
对呀 要不然你看到的是什么人
What are you looking at?
我看到的是个 穿衣服睡觉的人
I see a guy who slept in his clothes.
不,这只是外表
That's what everybody sees.
还有别的吗? 是呀,还有不少呢
- There's more? - A lot more.
很久前,这浑蛋救了总统
A long time ago, he saved the president's life.
柯莉说她被人骚扰
Her story about a weirdo hassling her was bullshit?
全是一派胡言吗?是吧
我不晓得她惹上什么麻烦
I don't know what she was into, but that was a professionai hit.
但今晚的一切确是职业手法
一副黑帮风格
Gangland style.
我想麦可为她工作
就像我现在一样 他被吓到了
I figure Mike was working for her, same as me.
非常怕
He got scared.
所以他立即脱身,拖我下水
Very scared.
我猜他脱身太迟了
Bails out, dumps it in my lap.
他被炸得粉身碎骨
He bailed too late.
They're scraping him off my stucco.
如果麦可明知危险
If Mike knew this was dangerous, why didn't he say anything to you?
为何他不明说 把这件事转交给你
他和我的太太有染
He was fucking my wife.
如果我死了 他就可接手我妻了
I die. He gets the wife.
可以走了
Free to go. Pick up your gun at the property desk.
到取物处取回你的枪
你花了一天时间
You took all day.
乔,我接到贝艾警署打来的电话
I got a call from the bei air p.D.
参议员一直接下流电话
Senator baynard has been getting obscene phone calls.
最好不是你
It better not be you.
还有什么事吗?警官 有的
Anything else, lieutenant?
有个新发明叫剃刀
There's a new invention out: The razor.
太危险了
Too risky. I might start thinking about you and slash my wrists.
一想到你 我可能会剃伤手腕
他和班纳有过节?
- He got a beef with baynard? - The senator got him fired.
他炒他鱿鱼
他曾是警探?
What was he, a cop?
秘密保镖?
Secret service?
而班纳曾炒你鱿鱼?
And baynard had you fired?
为什么?
How come?
不关你的事
None of your business.
你进来这干嘛?
What are you doing here?
我打掉他四颗牙齿
I knocked out 4 of his teeth.
你打球吗?你有好身材
Ever play ball? You got a good build.
你是同性恋?
You a fag?
不是, 我只是想把气氛弄好点
Just trying to break the ice.
我不喜欢,别烦我
I like ice. Leave it the fuck alone.
你应该很好相处的
You're fun to be with.
去你的
Fuck you.
下一步该怎么办?
So what's the next move, ace?
我要回家
I'm going home.
似乎我的工作已告一段落
It would seem my job is done.
干!你的工作已完成? 我们看着柯莉被杀
Fuck that. We saw Cory get murdered.
你要找死,请自便
You want your ass shot off, be my guest.
当你死后 我会接收你600元的裤子
You die, I take your $600 pants.
是650元
650.
你很面熟,我认识你吗?
You look familiar. Do I know you?
也许吧,很多人认识我
You might. People recognize me.
我想到了 你是打撞球的摩顿
"Cue ball" Morton! Sold hash in boyle heights.
而在鲍育高地卖过马铃薯
不对,我打橄榄球 名叫吉米,打过洛城雄马队
I played football. Jimmy dix, I.A. stallions.
什么位置?算了
- What position? - Forget it.
橄榄球,自由身球员 把这项好运动毁了
Football. Free agents ruined the goddamn game!
我们可能碰到更多你的球迷 想借我的墨镜吗?
We may run into more fans. Want my sunglasses?
你去死吧 你也去死
- Fuck you. - Snappy comeback.
柯莉住哪儿?
Where did Cory live?
梅洛的哈伯公寓 怎么了?
Harper apartments, on Melrose. Why?
想去那四处看看
Think I'ii look around there.
很好,我跟你一道去
I'll come with you.
干
The fuck, you are. Have a nice night, junior.
去玩乐吧,小子
我知道她后备钥匙在那
- I know where the extra key is. - I won't need a key.
我用不着钥匙
我猜你不担心警戒系统吧
And you're not worried about the alarm.
最先进的,我自己装的
It's pretty high-tech. I put it in myself.
你可能知道 如何用计胜它,对吧
But you probably know how to circumvent.
用计胜它?  这字是生字
Circumvent?
你看书吗?
It's called vocabulary.
“流莺”志才刚登过这个
- Read much? - My subscription to "jugs" just ran out.
上车吧
Get in the car.
她怎能负担起这儿的房租
How did she afford this? It must run a fortune.
这儿很贵的
告诉你,是我付房租的
- Tell me about it. I pay the rent. - Isn't that charming.
多迷人的房子
她听起来蛮特别的
She sounds like a reai speciai giri.
你还付些什么钱?
What else you pay for? Clothes? Car?
衣服?车子
并不是你想的那样
It wasn't like that. Cory could've had rich guys. Me, she loved.
柯莉本可以和更多的 有钱人交往,但她爱我
爱情,算了
Love? Forget about it then.
你不相信爱情?
- You don't believe in love. - I believe in love. And cancer.
不,我相信爱情 就像我相信癌症般
怎么?它们全是致命疾病
- Both diseases? - Something like that.
差不多
我想见见那位婊子 看看那是如何惹你发火
I want to meet the bitch that fucked you up.
你来现一下
Your show, ace.
警戒系统?
- Security system? - I circumvented it.
是的,我发明它
Don't touch anything. Don't leave a mess for the cops.
别碰任何东西 别给条子留下任何麻烦
我的天呀
Oh, my God.
你用吸尘器来吸 我会弄脏它
- You vacuum, I'll dust. - Stay put.
保持原样吧
去吧,泰山
Go, Tarzan.
吉米…和柯莉在一起的这个人是谁
Who's this guy with Cory?
谢利马康
Shelly marcone. Owns the I.A. stallions.
他是“雄马”队的老板
她和他交往一阵子
They dated. Treated her like shit. And she left.
但他待她极坏 她于是离开他
你去哪里? 浴室,你也要一起来
Where you going?
Bathroom. Want to come? Doc said I shouldn't lift anything heavy.
医生说 我不能举任何重的东西
I'll pass.
我不去
赌十比一, 他们一定是在找这东西
10 to 1, they were looking for this.
那是马康 我知道
- That's marcone. - Yeah, I know.
我不知道这是谁 班纳参议员
- I don't know who this is. - Senator baynard.
这两个浑蛋呢? 他的保镖
And the assholes with him?
他到那,都要人保护
His bodyguards. He always has protection.
电话帐单的影印本
Copy of a phone bill.
这是谁的电话
What's this number?
班纳家的
Baynard's home number.
你知道他家的电话?
You know his number?
是的,我打过几次电话给他
So I called him a couple times. Shut the fuck up.
别说出去
这一切有什么意义,乔?
What's all this?
我不晓得,小子
I don't know, junior. If we're lucky...
如果我们幸运的话
maybe enough blackmaii evidence to put two very powerfui men away.
或许手上足够的证据
可以把 加州二号大人物送进监牢
柯莉为什么要勒索他们?
Why would Cory blackmaii them?
你说她和马康上过床… 我说约会,没说他们上过床
- She was fucking marcone- - Dating, not fucking.
不管怎样, 她听到或者到什么
Whatever. She heard or saw something. The point is-
想勒索他们 她雇用麦可…
- she was blackmailing them. - She hires Mike.
去抓他的小辫子,对吗?
She got evidence to use on them. Now we have the evidence.
没错, 如今我们握有证据
小子,我们要对付的是 没人敢动他们的马康及班纳
We got marcone and baynard by the nuts.
这也是我之所以爱美国的原因
And that is why I love America.
喂?嗨,盖文
- Hello? - Hey, Calvin?
我是谢利马康
Shelly marcone. How you doing this evening?
是马康的声音,今晚如何?
I'd prefer you didn't use my name.
我希望你别提我的名字
神经过敏
A trifle skittish. If I didn't know better...
盖文,假如我不了解你的话
I'd say you were contemplating something shady.
我会以为你在耍什么阴谋
快点,快说重点吧
Get to the good stuff.
除非你让法案通过 我按快转
I'll fast-forward it.
别按快转,这会卡带子
Don't!
It eats the tape!
我那晓得? 它会卡带子
I'm supposed to know?
我们唯一的证据, 而你的烂车吃了它?
Your car ate our only evidence?
烂车 你最好闭嘴
- This car sucks. - Shut up!
如果它毁了,我就你揍死 这部烂车
If this is ruined, I'll crush your nuts.
看看这个
If this is ruined, I swear-
毁了
快转吃了带子
fast-forward eats the tape.
看来这就是我的生日礼物
My birthday present.
什么?
Cory was blackmailing marcone. But not for cash.
柯莉并不是为钱勒索马康
她只是想让我重回老本行
She was trying to get my job back.
她因我而丧命
She's dead because of me.
你去哪里
Where you going?
回家,我不舒服
Home. I don't feei too hot.
来,我送你
I'll take you.
我载你一程 不用
I'll give you a ride.
我开柯莉的车,我有钥匙
I'll take Cory's car. I got the key.
她的车子不是在酒吧吗?
I thought that was Cory's car at the bar!
吉米?
她有两辆车
Cory had two cars.
快下车… 什么?
Get out of the car!
你搞什么鬼?你怎么了?
What's your trip?
这是什么?  C-4
- What is it? - C-4.
塑胶炸弹
Plastic explosive.
他们在麦可车上 装了个相同的
They wired the ignition to Mike's car. They'd do the same with hers.
幸好他们装错车
Lucky for you they wired the wrong car.
把这留给警察?
Leave this for the cops to analyze.
让他们去分析
You're putting that in the trunk?
你把它们放在行李箱?
难不成 要留给附近的孩子玩?
No, let's leave it for the neighborhood kids to play with.
晚安,先生们
Good evening.
枪给我,贺伦伯
Where's the gun?
这么晚还出来晃?
- Bit late for a stroll. - You girls should get home.
你们这些女的早该回家了
Streetlights are on.
是啊,街灯还亮着呢
Shut up, fuckface.
闭嘴,丑八怪
I'm fuckface. He's asshole.
我是丑八怪,他是浑球
杰克
告诉他自以为风趣的下场
Apprise Rodney dangerfield here of his situation.
也许我们该正经点
We can dispense with the fun and games now.
你想要信封,对吗?
- You want the envelope, right? - Very smart.
信封,没错,你很聪明
Here's a man who knows when a situation is untenable.
这个人知道自己占不到便宜
说得好
Good word.
你喜欢?
You like it?
那你是有那信封了,对吧?
You do have that envelope?
我们最好放弃, 吉米
We better give up. We're dealing with geniuses.
这些人是天才
拜托,老兄,放过他
Leave him the fuck alone.
放过他?你算那根葱?
Leave him alone? Whatever you say.
杰克很努力地攻击
Jake attacks his job with a certain exuberance.
该死,我们被一些恶霸揍
We're beat up by the inventor of scrabble.
他仍不开心,再踢他
He's still happy, kick him again.
好了
All right!
你要那妓女的信封
You want the hooker's envelope?
她不是妓女 闭嘴
She wasn't a hooker.
Shut the fuck up!
在哪里?
Where is it?
在行李箱中
In the trunk.
给我钥匙
Give me the keys.
慢慢来
Slow and easy.
把钥匙给杰克拿来
Give them to Jake.
笨蛋,你将会吃到苦头的
Dumb bastard, you'll pay for that.
杰克,打开行李箱
Open the trunk.
该死 快跑,快跑
Son of a bitch!
你还活着?
You alive?
还不确定
I don't know yet.
是那炸弹?
Was that c-4?
难不成还是回收车的问题
That, or a hell of a factory recall.
死人不会开这种笨玩笑的
Dead guys don't make bad jokes.
没错
妈的,我们都没死
Shit, we're alive.
没错
你说的没错
快离开这,快走
Get out of here.
你确定?我来应付
I'll take the heat for this.
你确定吗?
You positive?
这是警方的事
This is a police matter!
你这笨蛋
And I'm sick and tired of sweeping up your dead bodies!
我已厌倦帮你收尸
下次我再见到你这张丑脸时
Next time I see your ugly mug...
我会给你一枪
I'll put a bullet in it! You got it?
明白吗?
我只想和你握握手
I just wanted to shake your hand.
什么?
Ben told me what you did for the president. I respect that.
班告诉我你为总统所做的事
我深感敬佩
谢了
嘿,丑八怪
Hey, ugly.
看来我们的证据毁了
Looks like our evidence got blown up.
我们得再找一些
We might have to get more.
你还不死心
Just won't let go.
你像支死缠不放的狗
You're like a dog with a frisbee.
女友死了
My girt's dead.
凶手逍遥法外 在高级餐馆进餐
Her killers are at spago's eating chicken marsala.
还在吃鹿乳酪披萨
And their goat cheese pizza.
这不公平
It ain't right.
是的,这说不过去
No, it ain't right.
这可不是在玩游戏
This ain't no game, flash.
真枪…
Reai guns.
实弹…
Reai bullets.
很危险
It's dangerous.
我的绰号就叫危险
Danger's my middle name.
我叫死不放弃
Mine's Cornelius.
别告诉任何人, 否则我宰了你
Tell anybody, I'll kill you.
你看“灵魂车”节目? 闭嘴
Ever watch "soul train"?
Shut the fuck up.
我们明天开始
We start tomorrow.
现在,我要回家看看家人
In the meantime, I'd like to see my family.
你的家人?
Your family, huh?
你有孩子?
You got kids?
小女孩  她爱你吗?
- A giri. - Does she like you?
不怎么爱
No, not too much.
她喜欢“王子”
She likes prince. Go figure.
喜欢有身材的
I like prince.
我也喜欢“王子”
好房子
An actuai house.
我还以为是粪便满地的洞穴
I was thinking of a cave with skulls and shit.
我觉得自己满身大汗
Feei like I been rode hard and put away wet.
什么意思?
What does that mean?
是说马的,老兄
It's horse talk.
现在也骑马啦
Brothers ride horses now?
车子太难偷了啊
Cars are too hard to steai.
你还载了顶小牛仔帽?
Do you wear a little cowboy hat?
我是优秀骑师
I'm really good.
也许我还可约会你女儿 她什么样子?
Maybe I could take your daughter.
她才13岁 如果你动歪念,你就死定了
Even look at her funny...
I'll stick an umbrella up your ass.
怎么还没睡?
Why aren't you in bed?
黛莲在看电视
Darian's watching TV.
我看到了
- I can see that. - She's pissed at you bigtime.
她很生你的气
你的脸怎么了?
What happened to your face?
老天,她终于说话了
My God! It speaks.
我的脸没事,一直是如此
Nothing happened to my face. It always looks like this.
他的脸怎么了?
What's wrong with his face?
他的鼻太尖
His nose is too pointy. His eyes are beady.
眼太亮,耳太大
His ears are too big. He needs a shave.
需要刮胡子
拜托,我快尿裤子了
I am peeing in my pants, you're so funny.
你太会耍宝了
这是我女儿黛莲
This is my daughter, Darian.
我叫吉米
I'm Jimmy.
为什么把号号挂在头上?
Why's that number on your head?
是汽车牌照怕被偷吗?
Is it a license plate in case it's stolen?
不对,是有关橄榄球的
It's a football thing. It's my high schooi number.
这是我高中时的打球号号
When's graduation?
你什么时候毕业的?
你喜欢独自一人,是吗?
You want to be alone.
我会在厨房,这边
I'll be in the kitchen.
Over here.
乔,她遗传到你好胜的个性
She has your winning personality.
你会习惯的
You get used to it.
黛莲,我在做冰淇淋, 想来点吗
I got some ice cream. Want some?
别管我,我讨厌你
Leave me alone! I hate you!
因我不准她和汤母出去约会, 她在生气
She's pissed because I wouldn't let her date Tommy.
我错过了全年度最好的舞会
I only missed the best party of the year.
为什么不答应呢?
Why'd you say no?
因为她只有13岁,白痴
Because she's 13 years old, jerk-off.
要来点冰淇淋吗? 我不和你说
- Want some ice cream? - I'm not talking to you.
哦,真可惜
That's a shame. I'll miss all the pleasant things you say.
我会怀念你曾对我说过的好话
爸,我讨厌你
"Dad, I hate you."
巧克力口味,你最喜欢的
It's chocolate chip, your favorite.
我才不在乎呢
I don't care.
你是浑蛋
You're an asshole.
你知道我讨厌浪费食物
You know how I hate to waste food.
还要辱骂我吗?
Want to abuse me some more? Shock me.
吓我吧
I hardly ever hear the word "asshole."
我很少听人说“混蛋” 狗屎
你铁定常听人说 够了
- Bet you get it all the time! - That's enough!
你又要把我禁足?
- Will you ground me some more? - You got it.
你知道了 是的,混蛋
Yes, sir, asshole.
你得禁足好几个礼拜 别管我
- You're grounded. - Leave me alone!
他以为他是残暴的守护神啊 你要我打烂你的嘴吗?
He thinks he's ward cleaver.
你想和你妈一样吗? 尽管做吧
You want to talk like a trash-mouth? Sound like your mother?
我在外忙了一天
I have to hear this shit all day, do I have to get it from you?
回来还得受你指责?
乔,对你女儿别动怒
Go easy on the giri.
别告诉该如何教训我的孩子
Don't tell me how to talk to my kid.
来呀,来呀, 让我听听你所有的脏话
Let me hear all the really juicy dirty words.
来呀,天呀,你是个混球
You're such a fuckup.
黛莲,你是我女儿
You're my daughter and you're in my home. You will respect me.
住在我的房子里,你得尊敬我,懂吗?
别再叫我混球
- Don't call me a fuckup. - Why not?
为什么我不该?
Mom calls you that!
妈一直这么叫你
你妈叫我浑球
She called me a fuckup?
何时?和杰叔通电话时
When?
On the phone with Uncle Jay.
杰叔?
我是浑球
I'm a fuckup, but Uncle Jay? There's a reai standup guy!
而杰叔是非常优秀出色的家伙
这杂种逃税
He cheats on his taxes.
去问你妈 他为什么没在监牢服刑
Ask your mother why Mr. wonderfui's not in jaii for tax evasion.
因为他不是混球
He doesn't fuck up.
黛莲
上床睡觉
Go to bed.
For $50 you could pay a guy to pull her fingernails out.
只要50元,你可以请到人
把她的指甲一个一个拔下来
Anything that much fun I'd rather do myself.
如果真那么有趣我宁可自己来
我不了解你,但我想喝一杯
I don't know about you, but I need a drink.
请便
哦,妈的,这是你吗?
Shit! That's you?
你曾是模范老爹
You were ward cleaver.
是啊,我曾是模范童子军
I was a regular boy scout.
你和总统!
You and the president.
干,和大人物一起
Damn, hanging with the man!
看起来就像在威尼斯海岸所立起来的大看板般
It looks like one of those cardboard cutout things.
我曾和唐强森合照过
I once had my picture taken with don Johnson.
还有那照片吗? 早丢掉了
- Still got the picture? - I threw it away.
你会离婚吗,老兄?
You going to get a divorce?
I don't know.
妈的,我不知道
你不太喜欢女人,是吧?乔
You don't like women much.
I liked the guy she was fucking.
至少我喜欢她的姘夫
他曾是我的好友
He was my best friend.
才不是呢,他是烂和家侦探
He was a scumbag private detective.
所有私家侦探都是浑蛋
All private detectives are scumbags.
但他想害你被杀
But he tried to get you killed.
没有完美的朋友
Friends can't be perfect.
我但愿苍天不是蓝色
I wish the sky wasn't blue.
水不是湿的
I wish water wasn't wet.
我也希望我不再爱我的老婆
I wish I didn't still love my wife.
Life sucks.
生命就是这样
To Alex, the accountant.
敬会计师亚历士一杯
Your accountant's name is Alex?
你的会计师名叫亚历士?
不是
但他本来应该是
But he could have been.
亚历士是我的儿子
Alex was my son.
我曾结过婚
I used to be married.
某个周日,我去趟迈阿密
One Sunday, I'm away in Miami.
她不能同行因有八个月身孕
She couldn't go. She was 8 months pregnant.
她向拉柏瑞大道上走去
Walking down la brea boulevard...
突然有辆货车撞上路栏
out of nowhere a truck jumped a curb.
不知道怎么撞倒她
Never knew what hit her.
她死了
She died.
婴儿在保温箱中活了十七分钟
But Alex lived for 17 minutes in an Incubator.
他睡着了
He fell asleep.
只够时间做一个梦
Had time for one dream.
然后他也死了
Then he died.
我常想到他
I think about him all the time.
你知道吗?妻儿垂死挣扎时
I threw for 300 yards that day.
我去了三百号
While my wife and kid were dying...
打出一生最好的一场球
I had the game of my life.
生命就是如此
Life sucks.
Can I use your shower?
可以用你的浴室吗?
可以 谢谢
在大厅左边的第一个门边
Bathroom's down the hall on the right.
嘿,我帮你拿毛巾来了
Here's a towei.
这就是你在柯莉住处要找的?
This what you looked for at Cory's?
你就是你要找的? 你干什么?
This what you were looking for?
那值一千美金啊! 闭嘴
- That's $ 1000 worth of shit! - Shut up!
在我扭断你的脖子前 快滚出我的房子
Get the fuck out of my house before I break your neck.
我用那东西解愁
I use it to get by.
我不用那东西
I don't use it. I get by.
仍能克服痛苦
穿上衣服快滚
Get dressed and get out.
好的,算了
All right. I forgot.
我和正人君子说话
Talking to Dudley-fucking-do-right!
那东西很容易上瘾的
That shit happens reai easy.
刚开始时…
It starts out...
止痛剂
painkillers.
为了膝头痛服用镇痛剂
Using demeroi because your knees are shot!
在你查觉前,把毒品和煎饼一起吃
Before you know it, you're chewing codeine with breakfast.
然后一辆货车突然驶来
Then a truck comes out of nowhere...
我对神说
and you're talking to God, saying, "help me out, big guy."
你说：
帮助我,主啊
I pay taxes and go to church.
我缴税,上教堂
为何我的妻死子丧?
"What's with this dead wife and kid shit?"
但他不回答我
But he ain't answering.
那天,他根本不听我的祷告
He ain't taking calls that day.
相反地,我接到球队的电话
Instead, I get a call from the fucking league.
他们说：嘿,小子
They're saying, "kid, your career's over."
你的事业结束了
我说：“为什么?”
I say, "why?"
因为我赌博
Because I gambled.
为什么职业橄榄球界要看受伤报告?
Why is there an injury report in pro football?
没有人有这种待遇
Nobody else has one.
但职业橄榄球界就要这样
But pro football does.
你知道为什么吗?
You know why?
因为如此,赌徒才能正确地传播消息
That's so gamblers will have an accurate spread!
现在讲的都是钱
It's all business. They push untii you blow your brains out.
他们不断厌榨你, 直到你被榨干为止
就像他们对比利柯尔所做的
Like Billy Cole!
那些伪君子夺走我的生命
Can't you see the hypocrites took away my life!
当你不再难过时
When you're done pitying yourself, the door's that way.
前门是那个方向
你这杂种
You bastard.
我不只如此
And then some.
吉米 迪克斯
能帮我签名吗?
Sign my card?
对不起,刚才我很失礼
Sorry I was so bitchy before.
没错
- Your dad's pretty pissed. - He'll get over it.
你老爹必定很生气
是的,但他很快就会平复的
你是他的英雄
You were his biggest hero.
是吗?何时开始? 自我小时候
Since when?
Since I was little. You should've heard him.
你真该听听他当时的口气 吉米这个,吉米那个
"Jimmy this, Jimmy that. Best quarterback in the game."
最佳四分卫
When you got busted, he quit watching.
自你被扔出球队后, 他就不看橄榄球了
他揍他所有的偶像吗?
Does he punch all his heroes?
（优良童军之女  吉米迪克斯赠)
早安,吉米
Who are you?
你们是谁?怎知道我的名字?
- This is the guy? You sure? - It's him.
是这家伙吗?
你确定是这家伙吗? 就是他
The kid with the million-dollar arm?
那个有支百万金臂的家伙?
我猜不到你们谁像我老二
Don't look like much.
Which of you looks more like my dick?
有话就说,别挡着我
Say what you got to say, or get out of my way.
Grab him.
没事,没事
It's okay, folks!
怎么了?
It's okay. It's okay.
没事,没事
Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢,谢谢
危险是我的绰号
Danger is my middle name.
别在家尝试这个
Don't try this at home. I'm a trained professionai.
我受过职业训练的
There's me...
这是我…
and there's super Dave.
而那是奇人戴夫
我有坏消息及更坏的消息
- I got bad news and bad news. - Give me the bad news first.
先给我坏消息
Someone bounced Jimmy dix off a car.
坏消息是有人把迪克斯扔去撞车
现在给我更坏的消息
Now give me the bad news.
我自贺伦伯邻居那取得口供
I got a statement from hallenbeck's neighbor.
麦可死的那天
The day he died, Mike Matthews came to hallenbeck's house...
他清早去找贺伦伯谈事,对吗?
to discuss a case.
贺伦伯是这样说的,好的
So hallenbeck says.
但贺伦伯的邻居却声称
How come hallenbeck's neighbor claims...
麦可的车整夜都停在同一处
Matthews' car was in the same spot all night?
他为什么要说谎?
Why did he lie?
麦可姘上他的老婆
Matthews is fucking his wife.
怪不得车子会在那
That's why the car was there. Matthews was fucking his wife.
麦可姘上贺伯伦的老婆
贺伯伦当时刚进城不是吗?
Hallenbeck just got back to town.
老天,乔杀了那浑蛋
Christ!
Joe wasted the bastard himself.
他竟从容地自我办公室走出去
He waltzed right out of my office.
我让那杂种走了
I let the son of a bitch go.
给我一个机会, 班,我去逮他
Give me a chance. I'll get him.
汤米
Tommy.
老天啊
你17岁时, 我必定让你参加宴会
You can go to a party when you're 17.
早安,乔
Morning, Joseph.
看来我们有点麻烦,麦洛
We got trouble, milo.
拿起贺伯伦的枪,把扳机扣起
Pick up his gun by the trigger guard.
把它给我
Give it to me.
早安,先生们, 有什么问题吗?
Is there a problem?
是的,警官,的确有问题
Yes, there is. Apparently, there are too many bullets in this gun.
显然地,这枪的子弹太多了
指纹
Fingerprints.
乔,你真顽皮
Naughty boy, Joseph.
你刚杀了位条子
You just shot a policeman.
卧倒
是你,爹地
It's you, daddy.
是你…
我想他醒了
He's awake.
确定一下
Make sure.
妈的
I'm awake.
我醒了
你几乎扭伤我的手
You nearly broke my wrist.
麦洛警告过我们,小心这家伙的
Milo warned us to watch out for him.
干
Fuck that! Fuck you.
妈的
Look at him. He's nothing. Guy's a piece of shit.
看看他这样子,简直是人渣
有烟吗?
Got a cigarette?
烟?当然有
Cigarette? Sure.
我有烟
I got a cigarette.
有火吗?
Got a light?
有,我有火
Yeah, I got a light.
嘿,宝贝
Hey, I thought you were tough.
我还以为你是硬汉呢
He's not so bad.
派柏,看吧, 他哼都不敢哼一声
我把烟弄掉了
I dropped my cigarette.
可以再给我一根吗?
May I have another?
当然
Sure.
没问题,老皮
Sure thing, buddy.
我要火
I'm going to need a light.
再碰我,我会杀了你
Touch me again, I'll kill you.
成功了,宝贝
Bamba! Baby!
两战两胜
Oh, baby! Two for two!
我们两战…
We got a two for two!
早告诉过你了
Told you!
天呀
Jesus Christ!
你杀了他,你他妈的杀了他
You fucking killed him!
He's dead!
有什么问题吗?
Is there a problem?
他刚杀了查特,麦洛
He just killed him! He put his fucking nose through his brain!
他打的他脑出血
我要火
I needed a light.
你让我失望,乔
Joseph, you don't disappoint me.
但你冒了个大险, 派柏可以开枪打死你的
You took an awfui risk. Pablo could have shot you dead.
如果要我死,我早就没命了
If you wanted me dead, you'd have killed me already.
那倒是真的
That's true.
我们能来个正式介绍吗?
- Can we do a format introduction? - Who gives a fuck?
谁在乎呀?
You're the bad guy.
你是坏蛋,对吧?
I am the bad guy.
我是坏人
And I'm supposed to tremble with fear?
我想我是该吓的发抖?
Something like that.
差不多是这样
Fine. I'll start trembling in a minute.
很好
我在一分钟内会开始发抖
In the meantime, could I have a drink?
现在,能给我杯酒吗?
I don't see why not.
我看不出有何不可?
Take the corpse away, and fix Mr. hallenbeck a drink.
派柏,先把查特尸体弄走
再给贺伦伯先生倒一杯酒
Make that two.
两杯吧
这不是马康吗?
If it isn't Shelly marcone himself.
小心点,孩子
Carefui, son.
只有朋友叫我马康
Just my friends call me Shelly.
你有朋友?
You got friends? When did this happen?
什么时候开始的?
小子,我告诉你
You sure are feisty for a fellow in your position.
像你现在的处境,你该禁若寒蝉
麦洛,教他点规矩
Teach him some manners.
再碰我,我就宰了你
Touch me again, I'll kill you.
你在说什么阴谋?
What fucking conspiracy are you talking about?
贺伦伯是笨蛋,对吧?
Hallenbeck's a fruit loop.
他追随班纳参议员数年
He's been after senator baynard for years.
你要我相信
You want me to believe the senator's mixed up in this?
参议是也涉入这件阴谋中?
我再说一遍,警官
I'll say it again for the cheap seats, lieutenant.
我不晓得贺伦伯人在何处
I don't know where Joe is! That's my fucking statement!
这就是我的口供
Write it down and shove it up your ass.
写下来,放在你屁眼中吧
我可以以不合作罪名抓你
I could naii you for obstruction.
你却抓不住一名 索价2元的妓女
You couldn't naii a $2 whore. Charge me with something or let me out!
要不用莫须有罪名指控我 要不就放我出去
我先生并没有杀警
My husband did not kill a cop!
除此之外,我帮不上任何忙 我们可以走了吗?
Aside from that, I can't help you. May we go now?
我可以和你妈 私下谈一分钟吗?
Can I have a minute with your mom in private?
请便
Pleasure.
你不否认在麦可死前 你和他上过床吧
Do you deny being sexually involved...
with Matthews prior to his death?
我打电话来
Why am I calling? I had to hear your sweet voice.
只是想听你甜美的声音
And I need a favor.
并请你帮个忙
No, it ain't like that.
不,不是这样的
No, it wasn't no liquor talking.
不,我并没在说醉话
你不胖,只是丰满
You're not fat. You're just a whole lot of woman.
帮个忙吧,好妈妈
Do me a favor, big mama.
班纳参议员
Senator Calvin baynard. He's a season ticket holder.
他买一季的球票,对吧?
Punch up the address where you send the tickets.
我要你找出寄票的地址
很好,好的
Good giri.
拜拜
很好
别担心,我会找到你老爸的
Don't worry. I'll find him.
怎么找?
How?
找最近的坏蛋问
When in doubt, try the nearest bad guy.
橄榄球业已奄奄一息,乔
Football is a dying beast, Joe.
不再有英雄
No heroes left.
再也没了
Not anymore.
自66年,伟伯林付了四十万给纳曼斯后
Since old Sonny werblin paid $400,000 to Joe namath in '66...
那些混蛋愈来愈贪心
the bastards have gotten greedier.
天啊,何时他们才会满足?
God almighty, when's it enough?
自由身球员只会说 付钱,付钱,付钱
Jesus! Free agents!
"Give me, give me, give me!"
现在球员们都在吸毒吃药
Now you got guys on pcp, shooting themselves on the field.
并在场上射杀自己
美国民众已生气,厌倦
The American public's tired of it, and they're changing the channei.
他们更换频道
The ratings are down.
收视率下降
所以你收买参议员
So you'll bribe senators to legalize gambling.
让赌博合法化?
Legalize sports gambling.
是运动赌博合法化
你知道 当所有英雄全都没着落
You see, with all the heroes gone...
只有合法赌博能挽救橄榄球业
only legalized gambling will save the beast.
你同意吗?乔
You follow me?
我们在谈大笔金钱
We're talking about big bucks.
数以亿计
We're talking billions.
有九个零,孩子
That's nine zeroes, son.
我不是你的孩子
I'm not your fucking son.
乔,你有听说过议会…
Have you ever heard of the senate's commission...
调查职业橄榄球的赌博吗?
to investigate gambling in pro sports?
那是你收买的对象吗?
Is that who you're paying off?
议会三月进行投票
The commission votes in march.
我收买了每位议员
I got them all in my hip pocket, except senator Calvin baynard.
除了班纳参议员外
我试过收买那浑蛋,乔
I tried to bribe that son of a bitch.
他退钱回来,因他嫌钱不够
He gave it back because it wasn't enough.
他要多少?六百万
- What's he want? - 6 million.
不然他就告发我
Or he'll go straight to the police.
你知道吗?我认为干掉他花费还便宜点
It'll just be cheaper to kill that son of a bitch.
干掉参参员不是小事 即使对你种混蛋而言
Taking off a senator is ballsy, even for an asshole like you.
你说的没错,孩子
You said it, Joe-boy.
这也是我们要找你当替罪羔羊的原因
That's why we'll frame you for the senator's murder.
身为运动赌博委员会的主席
As chairman of the commission, I'll simply say this:
我只能说
I'm reviewing both sides of the issue with utmost care...
我会就此事件的正反两面
做仔细的研究
and scrutiny.
我会以个人一员的坚定立场
I will adopt a position...
based on what is best for the sport.
选最有利的方案
现在…
In the meantime...
我迫不及待地想至体育馆
I can't wait to get to the coliseum to watch my favorite team...
去观赏我最欢的洛城队 痛宰谭巴湾队
kick hell out of Tampa bay.
卡!
谢谢你,参议员
Thank you, senator.
我的荣幸
Always a pleasure.
吉米,想想,乔会怎么做
Come on, Jimmy, think, think, think! What would Joe do?
他会杀了人还吸口烟
He'd shoot everybody and smoke cigarettes.
我可没有枪
But I have no gun.
你怎么来的?搭便车
- How'd you get here? - I hitched.
那不是我的意思 我是说,你是怎么找到我的
I meant, how did you find me?
我爸是侦探, 我还能说什么?
My dad's a detective. What can I say?
你没掩饰行踪
You didn't cover your tracks. You're easy to trace.
很容易就找到
Just what I need: Nancy-fucking-drew!
很好,正是我要的
我把这带给你,或许你会需要
I brought you this.
你怎么会有枪?
Where did you get that?!
从爸的衣柜偷的
Stole it from dad's closet.
他知道会杀了我
He'd kill me if he knew.
你可能会先杀了自己, 小混蛋
You'll kill yourself first, you jerk.
快拿着那支丑猴子滚开这里
Take this ugly monkey and get out of here.
走开走开
I want to know what's going on.
等一下,我要知道怎么了?
看CNN吧 走吧
Watch CNN. Go!
妈的,是照片中的保镖
Those are the bodyguards from the picture.
那又怎样? 他们没等参议员就走
They're leaving without the senator. Now go!
我得跟踪他们,快走
我要跟你去
I'm coming too.
不行,回家,黛莲
You can't come. Go home.
去死吧…黛莲
Kiss my ass.
我说的够清楚了吧?
Kiss my ass!
很好,你这小富家子
Is that clear enough?
Fine!
我们只跟踪 能有什么危险了?
You little brat.
We'll only follow. How dangerous can that be?
我们到了
We're in position.
参议员的人在路上
The senator's men are en route. Eta, five minutes.
约五分钟到
该死,现在他们又往哪去?
Now where you going?
我们去看看,这儿有枪
Let's find out.
我说过不带枪,我讨厌枪
Here.
I told you no guns, right? I hate guns.
留在这儿,我去看看
Stay here. I'll go look around. Stay!
留在原地
六百万,对不起
Six mii.
Excuse me.
你们这些白痴
Did any of you stupid shits bother to frisk this fuck?!
可有人要搜他身
他有可能是条子,搜他的身
He could be a goddamn cop. Will you frisk him?
别紧张
Take it easy.
满意了吗?
Hand him the briefcase, Joseph.
把箱子给他,乔
西装蛮漂亮的
Nice suit.
那箱子装了炸药,对吧?
Was that briefcase loaded with explosives?
十磅的炸药
10 pounds of c-4, going to the coliseum now.
现在送去体育馆
多讽刺,不是吗?
It's ironic, don't you think?
这些炸药由班内贴身保镖亲自交给他
This bomb will be delivered to baynard by his own bodyguards.
他死后
After his death, the police will receive a photograph of you...
警方会收到你送上箱子的照片
你将要为这件犯罪事件顶罪
handing over the case.
他们将深信不疑
You'll be blamed for the crime.
因为他们都知道,你多恨班纳
They'll believe it.
- They know you're a fan of baynard's. - Go fuck yourself.
你去死吧
好的,可真不礼貌
That's not polite.
听起来非常具侮辱性
It's very abusive sounding.
你要怎么样,乔?
What would you do...
假如有人叫你去死
if somebody told you to go fuck yourself?
你会挖了他们的眼睛?
Would you cut one of their eyes out?
不会
那你要怎么做?
What would you do?
你以为自己很酷吗?
You think you're so fucking cooi.
你以为自己很酷
You think you're so fucking cooi!
再一次…
This once...
我会要你痛苦地尖叫
I'd like to hear you scream...
in pain!
放点饶舌音乐吧
Play some rap music.
嘿,小子
Hey, flash.
想救人?
Rescue attempt?
别臭美了
Blow me.
你一定是吉米 吉米?
You must be James.
他每个人都这么叫
He does that with everybody.
叫我乔
Calls me Joseph.
我相信你是一个人来
You're alone?
不,整个维也纳合唱团 都跟来了
No, I got the vienna boys choir with me.
这儿的人个个是笨蛋吗?
Is everybody stupid here?
只有你是,小子 杀了他们,并埋起来
Just you.
Shoot them, bury them.
怕吗?是的
Scared?
你呢?有一点点
Shitless. You?
嘿,麦洛
More or less.
先生,喜欢我的布偶吗?
Hey, mister!
Like my puppet?
把她带走
Get her out of here.
我叫毛茸茸阿汤
My name is furry tom.
我说快走,孩子 不,孩子留下
I said go, kid.
Kid stays.
你可以让他说话吗?
Can you make him talk?
来,试试
Go on. Try.
来,拿着
Go ahead. Take it.
好吧
猜谜语时间
It's riddle time.
为什么麦洛先生横过路边?
Why did Mr. milo cross the road?
我不知道,为什么?
I don't know. Why?
因为他的“宝贝”被卡住了
Because his dick was stuck in a chicken.
毛球?是的
Fur ball?
毛茸阿汤认为这是小穴 你们一定看过很多次了
This is the first pussy you guys have seen in a long time.
特别是那的肥猪
Especially this fat fuck.
你那弄来的外套,祖父?
Where'd you get the suit? Gangsters "r" us?
我们是黑帮吗?
走,离开这
快点
妈…!
她怎么会来这?
Why is she here?!
我跟踪他来的,不是他的错
It's not his fault!
该死,我会杀了你们俩个
I'll kill you both!
你还得排队呢!
Get in line.
拿着这个 我要这个干嘛?
Here.
瞄准,然后开枪
What do I do with it?
Point it and shoot!
伏倒
Keep down!
爹
有什么好主意 有,开快点
Any bright ideas?
Go fast!
好主意
Good idea!
把他推出这条路
Push this fuck off the road!
坐隐
把安全带系上
Put your seat belts on!
乔,情况很糟
This is bad!
坐稳,情况非常,非常糟
Very bad!
你还好吗?快走
You all right?
好的
妈的
Shit!
他们还有活命的机会吗?
Any chance he's alive?
恐怕没有
Not now.
嘿,打电话警察
Call the cops!
告诉他们,体育馆有炸弹
Say there's a bomb at the coliseum!
班纳参议员有危险,懂吗?
Senator baynard's in danger! You got it?
拿着,生日快乐 为自己买几条新裤子
Happy Birthday. Buy yourself a new pair of pants.
我们必须赶去处理那炸弹
Let's get the bomb before it gets baynard.
有车吗?
Got a car?
嘿,有车吗?有
Do you got a car?
车钥匙拿来
The keys.
门都没有,给我钥匙 否则我让她脑袋开花
No.
Give me the keys or I shoot the kid.
爹地…嘘
Daddy!
好的
快走
你一定是世上最傻的人,乔
You're the dumbest guy in the world.
为何这么说?
You save the guy that ruined your career...
因你救毁你一生的人
为偷你老婆的人报仇
and avenge the guy that fucked your wife.
女孩说他爸叫乔何兰白
The giri said her dad's name is Joe hollen-
他姓什么?贺伦伯
he stole my car and went to the coliseum.
贺伦伯偷了我的车去体育馆
他偷我的车,在我泳池放火 那人是疯子
He set my pooi on fire. The man is a lunatic!
找十人来 贺伦伯去体育馆了
Give me 10 black-and-whites. He's going to the coliseum.
乔,如果我们再快点
If we go any faster, we'll travei back in time.
就及时到鬼门关报到
在那边,中线道
There!
好的 你追他们,我向他们叫
Pull up and I'll yell at them.
什么?追到他们车边 我向他们
I'll yell at them.
我听过最笨的方法
That's a lame plan!
我们试试啊! 那是防弹玻璃,听不见的
Can we try?
Bulletproof glass. He won't hear you.
你干什么? 画张图给他们看
- What're you doing? - Drawing a picture.
这是什么?炸弹
- Of what? - A bomb.
它不像炸弹,倒像苹果
It looks like an apple with lines.
他们会以为 打开箱子会有苹果
"Don't open the briefcase, it's full of fruit."
那你来画呀
You want to draw it?
满意吗?
Happy?
开玩笑吗?
You kidding?
谁能批评我? 我做什么事都对
Always criticizing!
哦,该死
我忘了告诉你
I forgot.
BOM在波兰语中意指“干”
"Bom" is "fuck you" in Polish.
这并不好笑 我差点被射杀了
It's not funny. I almost bought it.
对艺术界真是一大损失
Tragic loss to the art world.
你快追丢了,老兄
You'ii lose them.
系紧你的安全带
Buckle your seat belt.
它不能用
It's broken!
哦,妈的
我发誓,如果我能活过这次
I swear, if I survive this case, I'll dance a jig.
我会狂舞一番
什么?
I'll dance a jig.
我发誓,狂舞一番
那儿,那儿
There! There!
我们刚过了出口
The off-ramp we just passed!
嘿,你去哪儿?
Where you going? What are you doing?
你要干什么?
老天
Ain't I a bitch?
我脾气太差了
Now do we go to the cops?
我们去找警察吗?
我考虑看看
I'll think about it.
你在等电话吗?
Expecting a call?
嘿,干你娘的
Hey, motherfucker.
你从那打来 麦洛,游泳池底
Where are you, bottom of the pooi?
我正前往球赛
On my way to the ball game.
嘿,这儿有人要跟你谈谈
Someone here wants to talk to you.
嘿,爹地
Hi, daddy.
我没事,我没受伤
I'm okay. I'm not hurt.
爹地?
You back off...
你最好抽身,乔
or I'll show your daughter what a hot date I am.
否则就让你女儿好看
怎么了?
- What happened? - He has Darian.
他捉了黛莲
我们该怎么办?
What do we do?
我们去逮马康,这是唯一的方法
We take marcone. It's the only way.
我们什么都不做 他们也会杀她
We do nothing, they'll kill her anyway.
小心那箱子,会爆炸的
Carefui with that case. It goes "bang."
看看这些好家伙
Look at all this.
拿着
粉碎弹…
Shredders.
警方和反毒组用以爆破
Police and the DEA use it to blow locks.
一触即炸
They explode on impact.
十尺内无人生还
Kill everything within 10 feet.
粉碎弹
Put this on. Get in. You in or out?
穿上它,上来
你来吗? 我来,我还能有什么损失?
孩子,我们去看球赛
I'm in. What can I lose?
We're going to a ball game.
嘿,马康的车,来吧
That's marcone's car.
Come on.
我一直很想这么做
- Always wanted to do that. - Should've shit on it.
该死
该死 什么?
I forgot to tell you, you're wanted for murder.
忘了告诉你,你已被通缉了
嗨,迪先生,好久没见
Mr. dix. Long time no see!
对,好久了
Yeah, too long.
我们要见马康
- We're going to see Mr. marcone. - Sure, go ahead.
去呀
吉米,你这混蛋
Jimmy, you bastard! You broke my nose!
你来这干嘛? 你打断我的鼻子
What are you doing here? You were kicked off the team!
你被赶出这支队伍了
你想被赶出这星球吗?
How'd you like to be kicked off the planet?
祝你玩的愉快
Have a nice game.
嘿,乔
好吗?
How you doing?
你是大笨蛋
You are one dumb bastard.
你知道吗?
You know that?
我猜我们不能跳劲舞了
I guess we won't dance that jig.
你没事吧?黛莲
You okay?
当然,她没事
Of course she is. She's been with Uncle Shelly.
她和马康叔叔玩的很高兴
I'm okay.
是的,我没事,爹地
Lose the guns.
来,把枪丢掉
Take off your coats. Relax.
脱掉你的外套,放轻松点
投降吧,马康
What do you think baynard'll do...
你以为班纳知道你要杀他后 还会放过你吗?
when he learns you tried to kill him?
他没机会了
He doesn't have a chance.
要不了多久,我的老朋友麦洛
Shortly, milo will have him...
将用来福枪瞄准他
in the sights of a high-powered rifle.
他从哪开枪?
Where's he shooting from?
你是不是永远有问不完的问题?
You never run out of questions.
这么说吧
Let's just say...
麦洛选了一个绝佳位置
milo's in a highly enlightened position.
为什么要杀柯莉?
Why'd you kill Cory?
她想勒索我,我不吃这套
She took to blackmaii. I have no truck with that.
她是我“用”过的妓女中
She's one of the sweetest whores I ever tasted.
最捧的一个
我们之间,距离大理石地只有五尺
There's 5 feet of marble between me and you.
也许我能成功达阵得分
Maybe I make it, maybe I don't.
如果你再叫她妓女
You call her "whore" again, I'll find out.
不妨试试
吉米,吉米
Jimmy, do what you got to do.
做你想做的
Take it easy.
放轻松点,吉米
他当然知道
He should know.
他终究要付出代价
With a face like that, he must pay for it.
如果你还喜欢这小女孩
If you're fond of this little giri...
那就闭上狗嘴
keep your goddamn mouth shut!
去偷吃屎吧,你这肥老
Eat shit, you redneck!
过来,黛莲
Come here.
吉米,看到你真开心
Goddamn, I'm really glad to see you, Jimmy.
你知道吗?
I still have that autographed ball...
我仍保有那些签名的球 那是你给我的收藏品
you gave me for my collection.
是的
有件事很可惜
It's a shame about you.
你的臂值百万
You had the million-dollar arm, kiddo.
你却迷上…
You got hooked on the-what was it?
那是什么…
Demeroi!
毒品
Because you couldn't stand the pain.
你会上瘾, 表示你忍受不了痛
你讨厌苦痛
他忍受不了痛,乔
Couldn't take the pain.
生命就是一场苦痛,吉米
Life is pain.
走开,年轻人
Walk it off, son.
纪律
Discipline.
噢,天哪
Kids nowadays just don't have no discipline.
现在的孩子毫无纪律
你不感到难过吗?
Don't you cry, honey.
不,你不难过
来,去坐在马康叔叔的椅子上
Come on.
Come sit in my chair.
你将会是…  放她走
Let her go.
解除他们的痛苦吧
Put them out of my misery.
这事牵扯了六百万元
There is the matter of the $6 million.
也就说,除非你不感兴趣
Unless you're not interested.
让我们来逗逗这浑球
Let's humor this asshole.
告诉我
Tell me.
只有我俩知道它在哪儿
Just me and flash know where it is.
它在一轮白色的BMW汽车后 我们可以带你去
It's in the back of a white BMW.
We can take you to it.
麦洛说,钱被毁了
Milo said the money was destroyed.
你在吹牛
You're bluffing.
你以为我在吹牛?
Think I'm bluffing?
我还有一卷录音带
I also have in my possession a tape.
是你和班纳勾结的谈话
You and baynard.
很有少的证据
Very juicy stuff.
让我猜猜
Well, now, let me guess.
假如你出了事…
If something happens to you...
那东西会寄给警方,对吗?
that thing will be mailed to the cops.
很接近,其实会到黑道那
Close. Actually, it goes to the mob.
他们会很有兴趣知道
They'd be interested to know what you're up to.
你想做什么,合法赌博?
Legalized gambling.
他们会损失多少?
They stand to lose what?
2至3亿美金?
Two and a half billion dollars?
他们不会生气
They won't be upset about that.
只是损失全年的收益
Just their entire bookmaking income.
来吧,开枪吧
Go ahead and pull the trigger.
请便吧
Be my guest.
只是别惊讶明早醒来
Don't be surprised if you wake up next to a stallion head.
身边有个马头…宝贝
如果你有那卷录音带
If you had that goddamn tape you'd have already told me.
你早告诉我了
没用的,老兄
This ain't working.
用尽你的力量吧
Take your best shot.
干,乔,我不想就这样死了
I ain't going out like that! He's iying!
马康先生,他在说谎
- The money's not in the car. - Shut up!
钱在我们身上 闭嘴
在储物柜里
It's in a locker. And I got the key.
我有钥匙
钥匙在哪
Where is it?
藏在我内裤内
Stashed in my shorts.
别紧张,慢慢来
Easy. Just easy.
别给他,他会杀你的…
Don't. He'll kill you!
反正他都会杀我们,浑球
He'll kill us anyway!
你得答应放我走
Promise to let me go.
鬼扯淡
Bullshit.
给他钥匙, 否则打烂你的膝盖
Give him the key or I'll kneecap you.
看来没人会拿到钱
Nobody gets the money. It's one of those new plastic keys.
那是塑胶钥匙
把钥匙拿出来
Get the key!
会爆炸的那种
The kind that shreds.
伏下…黛莲
Get down!
带她出去,带她出去
Get her out!
快走
走,走
我走不动
I can't walk.
还好吧,快不行了吗?
You going to pass out?
我会没事的
I'll make it.
来,用这把你的手包里起来 塑胶钥匙?会爆炸的那种
Plastic keys? The kind that shred?
当时没法可想 那是最好的了
Short notice. Best I could do.
你做得很好 小子,真的很好
You did reai good.
是的,我从专家那学来的
Learned from a pro.
妈的,乔,你没吹牛
Shit! You wasn't bluffing.
参议员的包厢在哪?吉米
- Where's the senator's box? - Section c. I'll show you.
在C区 来,我带你去
参议员的包厢在哪?
Where's the senator's box?
那边
麦洛人呢?
Where's milo?
一个高而光亮的位置
"A highly enlightened position."
他一定在那些探照灯上面 听着小乖
He must be on those lights.
找个警察, 和他在一起,好吗?
Find a cop and stay put.
不要   听爸的话,好吗?
You hear me? Listen to daddy, all right?
我会没事的,我会没事的
I'll be all right.
照我的话做,给我一个吻
Do what I say. Give me a kiss.
去…去找个警察
Go find a cop.
我呢?  你去找班纳
- What about me? - Find baynard.
然后呢?
Then what?
吸引他的注意力
Get his attention.
来,快上,你这肥鬼
别动,贺伦伯 听着,有个杀手…
Freeze!
你被捕了 …要射杀班纳
A sniper's on that light! He'll shoot baynard!
少来
Come on!
他在那,吉米 迪克斯在那
There he is! Jimmy dix!
逮住这浑球, 他刚用枪指着我
He pulled a gun on me.
你这浑蛋
You scum!
他有猎枪
He's got a gun!
你这浑球,干
You bastard! You fuck!
坐下,你这浑蛋
Sit down!
请留在原位
我再重覆一次…
别走上球场 把球给我
Give me the ball!
吉米,给我球
Give me the fucking ball!
谢了
Thanks.
我说,坐下
I said, "sit down!"
干
你这…浑球
放下武器,你已被包围
Put down your weapon!
妈的
找这个?
Looking for this?
你这浑球
Asshole!
我告诉过你…
I told you:
你再碰我
You ever touch me again, I'll kill you!
我就杀了你
不是我,不是我
他在干什么?
What the hell is he doing?
不知道,像在跳舞
I don't know. Is he dancing?
看起来像在跳舞
Looks like he's dancing.
以舞姿而言 他是跳舞最差的侦探
For a dancer, he's one hell of a detective.
告诉我
What's this I hear about Satan claus?
圣诞老人是怎么回事?
哦,你也知道他呀?
You know about him too?
在那里,就是他
There! That's the man!
这浑球一直打电话骚扰我
This bastard's been making phone calls and harassing me!
他主使这一切
I bet he stage-managed the whole damn thing!
逮捕他
Arrest him!
头还是肚子
Head or gut?
什么?
Excuse me?
妈咪来了
Mom's here.
妈咪
I missed you so much.
我好想你
你真是个浑蛋, 你知道吗,乔
You know you're a reai bastard?
我不仅如此
And then some.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
非常非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
请原谅我
Please forgive me.
我会买只狗
I'll buy a dog.
干,莎拉
Fuck you, Sarah.
干,莎拉, 你是说谎的婊子
假如不是警察在这, 我会吐你口水
If the cops weren't here, I'd spit in your face.
乔,他们说的那箱子在哪?
Where's the briefcase they were telling me about?
白色BMW汽车后座
White BMW. Back seat.
什么也没有呀
Ain't a thing here.
有了
Bingo!
马康拿错了
Marcone's got the wrong one!
怎么回事?
What?
我们下一步会是什么?
What's next for us?
明天吧,我想
Tomorrow, I guess.
逐步来
Take it one step at a time.
爸,我可以带吉米去见我朋友吗
Daddy, can I go show Jimmy to my friends?
他不是宠物,亲爱的
- He's not a puppy. - He's fucking famous.
少来了,爸,他…他妈的是名人呢
嘿,注意你的嘴巴
You want to watch your mouth?
少来了,爸 黛莲,你爸说注竟你的嘴巴
Come on, dad.
你就照办
Your father said, "watch your mouth." Do it.
是的,长官
Yes, sir.
我喜欢这样
I like that.
我在想,我可以用一名拍档
I'm thinking I could use a partner.
你肯吗?
You up for that?
我不知道 我对侦探之事一无所知
I don't know anything about being a detective.
没什么大不了的
There's nothing to it.
现在是九十年代,你不能走上前要打一个人
Since it's the 90s, you don't just smack a guy in the face.
你必须先说点漂亮的话 懂我的意思吗?
You say something cooi first.
懂的,像…“我将回来”
Like, "I'll be back."
是的,只是要比这好一点
Only better than that.
看到溜滑板,你会说…
Like, you hit him with a surfboard and say, "surf's up!"
滑板正流行,老兄
是的,差不多就是这样
Something like that.
还有什么吗?
What else?
目前没有什么好说的
That's about it.
水湿,天蓝
Water's wet, the sky is blue...
而圣诞老人就在那儿,吉米
and old Satan claus is out there, just getting stronger.
他愈来愈强壮
我们对此,能怎么办?
What do we do about that?
准备好,孩子, 这是我的座右铭
Be prepared, son.
That's my motto. Be prepared.
准备好
心情之河
Best watched using open subtitles mkv player
比任何小刀都为之沉寂
心情之河,你的污浊河水
带走我的宝贝生命
上个周末夜
来到老橡树旁
它就在河边
那是我俩相见之处
在地上,我发现你的手套
上面有你给我的小纸条
写着：吾爱,我误解你了
现在我必须放你自由
我再也活不下去
这样的伤害
这样的罪恶
我无法告诉你
那男生只是一位朋友
心情之河
比任何小刀都为之沉寂
心情之河,你的污浊河水
带走我的宝贝生命
你可以感受到那股气氛
就像夜深时的闪亮
你可四处感受到
因为今晚在克里夫兰 将是狂欢时刻
周五夜,是橄榄球狂欢夜
雄马队和大猫队
将一绝胜负
周五夜,是橄榄球狂欢夜
坐稳,放轻松
让我们静下心来观赏
这将是场艰辛的奋战
我们将享有一个 狂欢的橄榄球夜
在这黄金时段的丛林中
每个失误都会引来隆隆吼声
每个座位都像五十号线
保证你会过的很快活
周五夜,是橄榄球狂欢夜
坐稳,放轻松
让我们静下心来观赏
这将是场艰辛的奋战
我们将享有一个 狂欢的橄榄球夜…
周五夜
是橄榄球狂欢夜
谢谢观赏